Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/luan-tranngoc-579414201 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft SQL Server

PostgreSQL

MySQL

Luan Tran Ngoc

Software Engineer

Hanoi

Summary

Have over 7+ years of working experience in Software Development, participated in various IT projects as core developer

Majority of my work experience is Java web and technologies about modern web, my strongest point is Java technology. Currently, I am still researching all technology about Java language

Experience

Techcombank (TCB)
Back End Developer
May 2021 - Present (7 months)
Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

CMC Global Company Limited.
Senior Java Developer
December 2017 - May 2021 (3 years 6 months)

National Citizen Bank (NCB)
Oracle Developer
April 2017 - November 2017 (8 months)

FPT Information System
Java Developer
October 2013 - April 2017 (3 years 7 months)
KeangNam

Fpt Telecom C# Developer March 2013 - September 2013 (7 months) 17 Duy Tân

Education

FPT University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering \cdot (2009 - 2013)

Activity

11/03/2021, Viewed by Nga Lê (Lenka)